ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements
1917-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5619/001
186.5 cubic feet
186.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective bargaining agreements.
This collection consists of collective bargaining agreements between various employers and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union joint boards, regional offices, and locals.
6849652
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
A. Jensen, April 08, 2010
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 AV: ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004 fiche: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Speeches on Microfiche 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/008: ACWA Rieve-Pollock Foundation Files 5619/009: ACTWU Operations Department Sidney Hillman Awards Files 5619/010: ACWA Jacob Potofsky files 5619/011: ACTWU Southern Regional Joint Board Files 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5619/013: ACTWU Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files 5619/015: ACTWU Department of Occupational Safety and Health Files
Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6849652
- Northeast Regional Office A-J, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Northeast Regional Office K-Z, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Northeast Regional Office A-H, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Northeast Regional Office I-Z, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Boston Joint Board, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Boston Joint Board, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Boston Joint Board A-F, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boston Joint Board L-Z, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Boston Joint Board and G.T. Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Boston Joint Board A-F, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Boston Joint Board G-L, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Boston Joint Board M-S, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Boston Joint Board T-Z, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Boston Joint Board and M&M Pants Co., Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- New York Joint Board and Rose Bros., Inc., 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board A-G, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board H-R, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board S-Z, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board, 1959-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board A-Cl, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board Co-G, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board H-R, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board S-Z, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association A-C, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association D-F, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association E-H, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association I-L, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association M-O, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association P-Se, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association Sh-Z, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board A-C, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board D-K, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board L-R, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board S-Z, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association A-C, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association D-G, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association H-L, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association M-R, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association S-Z, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board A, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board B, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board C, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board E, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board F, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board G, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board H-K, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board L-M, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board N-Q, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board R, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board S, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board T, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board U-Z, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association A-B, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association C-D, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association E-F, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association G, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association H, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association I-L, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association M-P, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association R-S, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association T-Z, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board Supplemental Agreements, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- New York Cutters Local #4, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- New York Cutters Local #4, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board and Taverly, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Buffalo Joint Board and Salem Pants, Co., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1968-1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Capitol District Joint Board, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Capitol District Joint Board, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- South Jersey Joint Board A-L, 1968-1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- South Jersey Joint Board M-Z, 1968-1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A-F, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board G-P, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board R-Y, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A-G, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Joint Board H-R, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Joint Board S-Z, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A-Be, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Blk-Co, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Cr-Da, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board De-E, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board F, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board G, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Joint Board H-I, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Joint Board J-K, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Philadelphia Joint Board L-Ma, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Mi-Mu, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Joint Board N-Pe, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Pi-Q, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia Joint Board R, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Sa-Se, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Sp-Su, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Joint Board T-Z, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A-B, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Ca-Co, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Cr-E, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board F-G, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Joint Board H-I, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Philadelphia Joint Board J-L, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Joint Board M, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Ma-Mu, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Joint Board P, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Q-R, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Sa-Se, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Joint Board Si-Sy, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Joint Board T-Z, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Philadelphia Joint Board A-K, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Philadelphia Joint Board L-Z, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Jordan Clothing Company, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Le High Valley Joint Board, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Le High Valley Joint Board, 1968-1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board A-G, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board H-O, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board P-Z, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board A-G, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board H-O, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board M-Z, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board A-B, 1968-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board C-F, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board G, 1965-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board H-L, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board M-R, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board S-Z, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Western Organizational Department, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Midwest Organizational Department, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Southern Organizational Department, 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board A-K, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Chicago Joint Board L-Z, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Chicago Joint Board A-K, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Chicago Joint Board L-Z, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Chicago Joint Board A-G, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Chicago Joint Board H-M, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board N-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Chicago Joint Board A-B, 1971-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Chicago Joint Board C-E, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Chicago Joint Board F-L, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Chicago Joint Board M-Q, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Chicago Joint Board R-Z, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Milwaukee Joint Board, 1960-1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Milwaukee Joint Board, 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1968-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1968-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Minnesota Joint Board, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Kansas City Regional Joint Board, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- St. Louis Joint Board, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board, 1960-1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Kentuckiana Joint Board, 1968-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1967-1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Northern California Joint Board, 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Southern California Joint Board A-L, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Southern California Joint Board M-Z, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Southern California Joint Board A-L, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Southern California Joint Board M-Z, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Southern California Joint Board A-G, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Southern California Joint Board H-Q, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Southern California Joint Board R-Z, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  Associated Clothing Manufacturers' of the Province of Quebec, Inc.
- Montreal Joint Board and Montreal Clothing Contractors' Association, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board and Associated Clothing Manufacturers of Quebec, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Quebec Market Agreement
- Montreal Joint Board A-D, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  English and French
- Montreal Joint Board E-L, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board M-Q, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board R-Z, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1966-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board and Associated Clothing Manufacturers of Quebec, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board and Montreal Clothing Contractors' Association, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board and Independent Clothing Companies A-H, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board and Independent Clothing Companies I-Z, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board A-C, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board D-I, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board J-P, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board Q-Z, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board A-D, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board F-Me, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board Mi-S, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board T-Z, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board A-C, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board D-F, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board G, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board H-K, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Montreal Joint Board L-M, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Montreal Joint Board N-Pe, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Montreal Joint Board Pr-Ph, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board Sa, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board Sc-So, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board St-T, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Toronto Joint Board, 1958-1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Toronto Joint Board, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Manitoba, Local #459 and Manitoba Clothing Co. Limited, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1960-1962 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  English and Spanish
- Connecticut, Local #125, 1940-1967 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- New England Regional Joint Board, 1951-1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Boston Joint Board and the New England Tailors Joint Board, 1962-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements A-B, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements C-D, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements E-F, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements G-I, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements J-K, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements L-N, 1963-1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements P-R, 1963-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements S, 1963-1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements T-Z, 1963-1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board, Custom Tailors Local #162 A-F, 1965-1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board, Custom Tailors Local #162 G-K, 1965-1971 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board, Custom Tailors Local #162 L-Z, 1965-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union A-Blk, 1953-1963 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union Br-Da, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union Do-G, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union H-K, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union L-Ma, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union Mc-Ra, 1953-1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union Ri-S, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union T-Z, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union A-C, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union D-G, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union H-L, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union M, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union N-R, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)